<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Jenkins Changelog]]></title><description><![CDATA[Changelog for Jenkins weekly releases]]></description><link>https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 01:03:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.326]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Major RFE The agent-to-controller security subsystem is now always enabled. The admin-customizable allowlists for callables and file paths have been removed. The ability to access some files on the controller from agents has been removed. Some plugins are incompatible with this change and may need to be updated.</li>,<li>RFE Add missing SVG for parameterized job icon.</li>,<li>RFE Add "Report an issue" link to plugins in the plugin manager.</li>,<li>RFE Upgrade [Groovy](https://groovy-lang.org/) from 2.4.12 to 2.4.21.</li>,<li>Major bug - Restore support for symbolic links in the Jenkins home directory (regression in 2.325).</li>,<li>RFE Developer: Stapler now returns an informative error message when a request is made for an invalid adjunct.</li>,<li>RFE Developer: Deprecate <code>SlaveToMasterFileCallable</code>.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.326</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.325]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>RFE Modernise the appearance of the plugin manager.</li>,<li>RFE More reliably estimate plugin download progress.</li>,<li>Bug Newly created items are again automatically made accessible to their creators to fix a regression in the <code>matrix-auth</code> plugin (regression in 2.324).</li>,<li>Bug - Fix a resource leak when shutting down Jenkins.</li>,<li>Bug - Fix a resource leak when a plugin fails to load.</li>,<li>Bug Filtering now hides unavailable updates on "Updates" tab in Plugin Manager.</li>,<li>Bug An agent-to-controller security measure failed to persist configuration.</li>,<li>Bug Custom log records with large record parameters no longer interfere with garbage collection.</li>,<li>RFE Developer: Add <code>FilePath#validateAntFileMask(String, boolean)</code> overload for convenience.</li>,<li>RFE Developer: The option <code>-Dhudson.ClassicPluginStrategy.useAntClassLoader=false</code> allows experiments with plugin-first class loading alternatives.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.325</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.324]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>RFE Improve logging for termination of cloud agents.</li>,<li>Bug Fix appearance of table tooltips.</li>,<li>RFE Developer: Plugins now have their Guice dependencies aligned with core.</li>,<li>RFE Introduced <code>Listeners.notify</code> utility method to encourage safe listener notification.</li>,<li>RFE Developer: Disable form element path in unit tests by default.</li>,<li>RFE Deprecate FingerprintStorage.getFileFingerprintStorage.
Developers should use FingerprintStorage Extension API instead.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.324</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.323]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>RFE Add configuration-as-code support for managing log recorders.</li>,<li>RFE Add path to form elements giving stable selectors for UI testing.</li>,<li>Bug Update remoting from 4.11.1 to 4.11.2 to fix code signing.</li>,<li>Bug Improve performance by lazy loading build records from the run list.</li>,<li>Bug "View as plain text" shows correctly in polling log page.</li>,<li>RFE Developer: New extension point <code>Header</code> as an interface that provides capabilities to render a specific header and a default implementation of that, named <code>JenkinsHeader</code> that is enabled by default.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.323</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.322]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>RFE Issue a warning to the system log when using agent-to-controller file manipulation idioms considered for deprecation, and collect telemetry about this as well.</li>,<li>RFE Add descriptions of built-in administrative alerts to the global configuration alert selection page.</li>,<li>RFE Modernise System Info and Log Recorder pages.</li>,<li>Bug Jenkins startup could hang due to a deadlock in class loading.</li>,<li>Bug Display full user name, rather than id, in securityRealm page when using the built-in security realm (regression since 2.243).</li>,<li>Bug Display the "Configure System" icon in the drop down menu.</li>,<li>RFE Developer: Register <code>UberClassLoader</code> as parallel-capable.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.322</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.321]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>RFE Modernise the table design and add support for Ionicons.</li>,<li>RFE Remove superfluous user interface elements, including images, <code>mask-icon</code>, and unnecessary resize handles.</li>,<li>RFE Only apply <code>trimLabels</code> operation to affected nodes when adding or removing them.</li>,<li>Bug Maven tool configuration works again (regression in 2.320).</li>,<li>Bug Show ongoing first build in build history (regression in 2.314).</li>,<li>Bug Fix filtering in update tab of plugin manager (regression in 2.320).</li>,<li>Bug Permit additional safe types in agent to controller access control (regression in 2.320).</li>,<li>RFE Developer: Upgrade the Guice library from 4.0 (released April 28, 2015) to 5.0.1 (released March 2, 2021).</li>,<li>RFE Developer: Bump spring-security-bom from 5.5.3 to 5.6.0.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.321</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.320]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Major RFE Upgrade the Guava library from 11.0.1 (released on January 9, 2012) to 31.0.1 (released on September 27, 2021).
Plugins have already been prepared to support the new version of Guava; use the Plugin Manager to upgrade all plugins before <u>and</u> after upgrading Jenkins.</li>,<li>RFE Modernise the 'New view' and 'New node' pages.</li>,<li>RFE Improve artifact list readability in dark theme.</li>,<li>RFE Use CSS animation for console progress.</li>,<li>RFE Allow plugin upload by URL in addition to file name.</li>,<li>RFE Update bundled version of Bouncy Castle API plugin from 2.20 to 2.25.</li>,<li>Bug Prevent <code>LinkageError</code> during class loading (regression in 2.309).</li>,<li>Bug Do not attempt to canonicalize tar entries when untaring, as the result may be unexpected for symlinks.</li>,<li>Bug Fix form submission for file access rules of agent to controller security subsystem (regression in 2.111).</li>,<li>Bug Avoid false positives in plugin search (installed tab).</li>,<li>Bug Fix missing hyperlink in build history (regression in 2.314).</li>,<li>Bug Add space between icon and project name (or build number) in all links to builds.</li>,<li>Bug Add space between icon and project name in upstream & downstream section of project page.</li>,<li>Bug Replace outdated URLs with working redirects.</li>,<li>Bug An exception thrown by a <code>RestartListener</code> no longer leaves Jenkins in a zombie-like state.</li>,<li>Bug Display the time zone of the user when an administrator updates a user account.</li>,<li>RFE Developer: Provide a stable version of ObjectWebASM (currently 9.1) on the classpath.</li>,<li>RFE Developer: Use the upstream version of <code>AntClassLoader</code> without custom patches.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.320</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.319]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Security Important security fixes.</li>,<li>Major RFE Security hardening: Require role check for remoting callables.</li>,<li>RFE Always allow configuring agent-to-controller security subsystem.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.319</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.318]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>RFE Add <code>XStream2</code> constructor matching super.</li>,<li>RFE Remove deprecated, unsafe classes previously copied from Apache Ant. Docker Slaves plugin is incompatible with this change.</li>,<li>RFE <code>ExecutorListener</code> may now be implemented as a static extension.</li>,<li>RFE Update tooltips to be consistent across Jenkins.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.318</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.317]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>RFE Screen Resolution cookie now has the <code>secure</code> flag set when Jenkins is running on HTTPS.</li>,<li>RFE Deprecate the <code>-cp</code> option in the remoting agent.jar command line.
Upgrade from Remoting 4.10 to Remoting 4.11.</li>,<li>Bug Display ongoing build in build history (regression in 2.314).</li>,<li>Bug Fix agent handshake when connecting over Websocket on Java 11.
Upgrade from Remoting 4.10 to Remoting 4.11.</li>,<li>Bug Reduce the amount of disk writes to <code>logs/tasks/*.log</code> when nothing interesting is happening.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.317</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.316]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>RFE Update the French translation in the legend.</li>,<li>RFE Display full plugin name and link when a plugin fails to load.</li>,<li>RFE Improve error reporting for certain kinds of bugs in computer listeners.</li>,<li>RFE Update bundled versions of Pipeline: API, Pipeline: Step API, SCM API, and Structs plugins.</li>,<li>Bug Developer: Fix XStream2 support of unmarshalling implicit collections.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.316</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.315]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Security Security fixes.</li>,<li>RFE Security hardening: The "short description" of build causes is now defined as plain text instead of HTML.
</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.315</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.314]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>RFE Modernise the "Build History" search bar</li>,<li>RFE Show new status icons in build history</li>,<li>RFE Modernise the "Manage Jenkins" screen</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.314</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.313]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>RFE Allow a plugin to dynamically insert a JAR file into its classpath.</li>,<li>RFE Remove the <code>--daemon</code> argument from Jenkins command line arguments.  Replace Akuma library from Jenkins core with simpler implementations using <code>ProcessTree</code> capabilities</li>,<li>Bug Allow Jenkins to start when the JCasC configuration defines view-related permissions (regression in 2.302).</li>,<li>Bug Correction of Label expression including a "implies" relationship without spaces around.</li>,<li>Bug WebSocket connections now work when the Jenkins controller is running Java 11 and using self-terminated TLS.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.313</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.312]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>RFE Update executable war from 1.45 to 2.0</li>,<li>Bug Replace the old icons with the new SVG icons in the job trend page.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.312</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.311]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Bug Fix wrong parameter type for <code>Text Parameter</code> when triggering a build via the <code>buildWithParameters</code> API call.</li>,<li>RFE Graphs now scale correctly on high resolution screens.</li>,<li>Bug The checkbox labeled "Enable Agent → Controller Access Control" in the form "Configure Global Security" would always start out as disabled. Submitting the form without checking it would then cause a configuration change (regression in 2.307).</li>,<li>RFE Load classes from plugins in parallel for faster startup on multicore machines.</li>,<li>RFE Internal: Experimental support for <code>URLClassLoader</code> can be enabled by setting <code>hudson.ClassicPluginStrategy.useAntClassLoader=false</code>.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.311</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.310]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Bug Jenkins 2.310 was not placed in the artifact repository or on the download site.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.310</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.309]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Bug Fix missing settings/cog icon in Plugin Manager.
Fix incorrect folder icon showing in projects (regression in 2.307).</li>,<li>RFE Add <code>ABORTED</code> threshold to <code>ReverseBuildTrigger</code>.</li>,<li>RFE Developer: Bump Java Native Access (jna) from 5.8.0 to 5.9.0.</li>,<li>RFE Internal: <code>AntClassLoader</code> (and its subclass <code>PluginFirstClassLoader</code>) and <code>MaskingClassLoader</code> register themselves as parallel-capable.</li>,<li>RFE Upgrade from xstream 1.4.17 to 1.4.18.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.309</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.308]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>RFE Use SVGs over PNGs for the sidebar when possible.
Breadcrumb bar/logo/menu items are now correctly aligned on the left together.
Move old <code>war/images</code> folder to <code>webapp</code> so they can be used in frontend - the SVGs are now in the <code>webapp/images/svgs</code> folder.</li>,<li>RFE Update appearance for feed bar and description button to be modern and consistent.</li>,<li>RFE When the <code>buildWithParameter</code> API is called, if the requests with the same parameters in the queue are merged, the http response code of the request uses a more appropriate 303(see other) instead of 201(created).</li>,<li>RFE Warn about use of <code>master</code> in a label expression when that's no longer in use.</li>,<li>Bug Use full URL character encoding for the generated inbound agent launch string.</li>,<li>Bug Use the JVM's default keystore type for the Jenkins server when terminating TLS connections within Jenkins.
Used if Jenkins is started with the <code>--httpsPort</code> argument.
Winstone 5.21: Update Jetty from 9.4.42.v20210604 to Jetty 9.4.43.v20210629.</li>,<li>RFE Developer: Bump spring-security-bom from 5.5.1 to 5.5.2.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.308</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.307]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Major RFE Replace the term "master" with "controller" (for the main Jenkins application) or "built-in node" in user interface strings and documentation as appropriate.</li>,<li>Major RFE Add migration code to change the node name (e.g. <code>NODE_NAME</code> environment variable) and label of the built-in node only after explicit migration by an administrator.
New installations get the new node and label immediately.
If a job definition, Pipeline definition, or tool installer reference must be tied to the built-in node, it should use the label "<code>built-in</code>".</li>,<li>Major RFE Add the system property <code>jenkins.model.Jenkins.nodeNameAndSelfLabelOverride</code> to specify a different node name and label for the built-in node (e.g. for Configuration as Code use cases) than the one otherwise determined.
This will not affect other uses of the node name, such as the URL to the built-in node (now <code>/computer/(built-in)/</code>).</li>,<li>Bug GDSL file in <code>jenkins-core</code> library no longer reports an <code>IllegalStateException</code> when used in IntelliJ IDEA.</li>,<li>RFE Improve layout of console output header.</li>,<li>RFE Use the SVG version of the Jenkins text logo instead of the PNG.</li>,<li>RFE Developer: Jenkins now uses an updated version of the <code>AntClassLoader</code> class with fewer custom patches.</li>,<li>RFE Removed: The Woodstox implementation of the StAX API has been removed from Jenkins core.
Users of the Azure Artifact Manager, Azure Container Agents, Azure Storage, and Azure SDK API plugins must upgrade those plugins to the latest versions in lockstep with this core upgrade.
Plugins that consume Woodstox should depend on it directly or via the Jackson 2 API plugin.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.307</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.306]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Bug Provide working "Help About" links for Jenkins CLI, Jenkins core, and Jenkins war.</li>,<li>RFE Developer: <code>AntClassloader</code> will now ignore files that are part of the classpath but not zip files when scanning for resources. It used to throw an exception.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.306</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.305]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Bug Show tooltips when users hover on the SVG icons.</li>,<li>RFE Ability to disable Java 11 administrative monitor with a system property.</li>,<li>RFE Developer: Make <code>AntClassLoader</code> multi-release JAR aware when it deals with <code>java.util.jar.JarFile</code>.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.305</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.304]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Bug Fix an issue unzipping archives in a corner case when entries have the same path prefix as the target location.</li>,<li>RFE Avoid polluting the log when usage statistics can not be sent.</li>,<li>RFE Bump matrix-auth from 2.6.7 to 2.6.8.</li>,<li>RFE Bump bundled Ant from 1.10.10 to 1.10.11.</li>,<li>RFE Remove support for native JNR (Java Native Runtime) <code>chmod(2)</code> and <code>stat(2)</code> implementations as opposed to NIO (Java non-blocking I/O) via the <code>hudson.Util.useNativeChmodAndMode</code> system property.
This system property no longer has any effect.</li>,<li>RFE Developer: Allow consumers of <code>XmlFile</code> to disable <code>fsync(2)</code>.</li>,<li>RFE Internal: Terminology cleanup to fix build time trend's distributed builds.
Only show the agent column when the controller has agents defined.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.304</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.303]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>RFE Bump commons-compress from 1.20 to 1.21.</li>,<li>RFE Bump spring-security-bom from 5.5.0 to 5.5.1.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.303</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.302]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>RFE Optimize access control checks affecting (at least) Pipeline <code>node</code> steps.</li>,<li>RFE Developer: The <code>hudson.util.SubClassGenerator</code> and experimental <code>hudson.model.TreeView</code> class have been removed without replacement.</li>,<li>RFE Internal: Upgrade from Remoting 4.9 to Remoting 4.10 with bugfixes and dependency updates.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.302</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.301]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Major bug Fix a regression in 2.298 where some plugins (including Azure Storage) could not correctly parse streaming XML output.</li>,<li>RFE The Jenkins process management functionality now supports FreeBSD.</li>,<li>RFE Bump jenkins from 1.64 to 1.65.</li>,<li>RFE Winstone 5.19: Update Jetty from 9.4.41.v20210516 to Jetty 9.4.42.v20210604.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.301</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.300]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Security Important security fixes.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.300</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.299]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>RFE Update stapler from 1539.v2f05ce93882d to 1563.v3da2d02f9572.</li>,<li>RFE Developer: <code>InterceptingExecutorService</code> and its subclasses no longer extend <code>com.google.common.util.concurrent.ForwardingExecutorService</code> or <code>com.google.common.collect.ForwardingObject</code>.</li>,<li>RFE Remove <code>jna-posix</code> dependency from Jenkins core.
Plugins that use <code>jna-posix</code> functionality must be migrated from <code>jna-posix</code> to <code>jnr-posix</code>.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.299</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.298]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>RFE Document REST methods to mark an (agent) node temporarily offline and related tasks.</li>,<li>RFE Add <code>X-Frame-Options</code> header to AJAX responses.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.298</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.297]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Major RFE Remove Apache Commons Digester library and related code from the Jenkins core.</li>,<li>Bug Fix incorrect process termination issues when running on macOS.</li>,<li>Bug Add check to prevent out of bounds memory access error on macOS.</li>,<li>Bug A race condition in class loading could result in a <code>LinkageError</code>.</li>,<li>Bug Do not change fonts when artifacts are as shown as a tree.</li>,<li>RFE Bump sshd-core from 2.5.1 to 2.7.0 in Jenkins CLI.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog/#2.297</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>