<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Jenkins LTS Changelog]]></title><description><![CDATA[Changelog for Jenkins LTS releases]]></description><link>https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 06:35:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.303.3]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Security Important security fixes.</li>,<li>Major RFE Security hardening: Require role check for remoting callables.</li>,<li>RFE Always allow configuring agent-to-controller security subsystem.</li>,<li>Bug Correction of Label expression including a "implies" relationship without spaces around.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.303.3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.303.2]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Security Security fixes.</li>,<li>RFE Security hardening: The "short description" of build causes is now defined as plain text instead of HTML.
</li>,<li>Bug Allow Jenkins to start when the JCasC configuration defines view-related permissions (regression in 2.302).</li>,<li>Bug Use the JVM's default keystore type for the Jenkins server when terminating TLS connections within Jenkins.
Used if Jenkins is started with the <code>--httpsPort</code> argument.
Winstone 5.21: Update Jetty from 9.4.42.v20210604 to Jetty 9.4.43.v20210629.</li>,<li>Bug Fix wrong parameter type for <code>Text Parameter</code> when triggering a build via the <code>buildWithParameters</code> API call.</li>,<li>RFE Bump bundled Ant from 1.10.10 to 1.10.11.</li>,<li>RFE Upgrade from xstream 1.4.17 to 1.4.18.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.303.2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.303.1]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Bug Fix an issue unzipping archives in a corner case when entries have the same path prefix as the target location.</li>,<li>Bug Detect files in a symlink that points to a directory (regression in 2.301).
Bump Commons IO to 2.11.0.</li>,<li>Bug Show tooltips when users hover on the SVG icons.</li>,<li>RFE Use Java 11 in Docker images instead of Java 8.</li>,<li>RFE Allow Java 11 administrative monitor to be disabled with a system property.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.303.1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.289.3]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Bug Improve build status progress animation.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.289.3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.289.2]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Security Important security fixes.</li>,<li>RFE Winstone 5.18: Update Jetty from 9.4.39.v20210325 to 9.4.41.v20210516 for bug fixes and enhancements.</li>,<li>RFE Update from xstream 1.4.16 to 1.4.17.</li>,<li>Bug Prepare for form submission changes in future Firefox releases.
Adapt form validation for all web browsers and form validation test automation for HtmlUnit based tests.</li>,<li>Bug A race condition in class loading could result in a <code>LinkageError</code>.</li>,<li>Bug Do not change fonts when build artifacts are as shown as a tree.</li>,<li>Bug Jenkins redirects users to the previous page after login even if they were able to view it while not logged in (regression in 2.266).</li>,<li>Bug Fix incorrect process termination issues when running on macOS.</li>,<li>Bug Add check to prevent out of bounds memory access error on macOS.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.289.2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.289.1]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Major bug Fix <code>NoSuchMethodError</code> when using plugins that rely on bridge methods for compatibility (regression in 2.278).</li>,<li>Bug Fix form submission for some specific form validation cases (regression in 2.289).</li>,<li>Bug Wrap the build name in the build results list if it is too long.</li>,<li>Bug Improve performance for standard input of the Jenkins CLI, for example with the `install-plugin` command.</li>,<li>Bug Fix an issue archiving files greater than 4 GiB in size when creating ZIP64 archives.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.289.1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.277.4]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Bug Fix disabled dropdown items to appear disabled (regression in 2.277.1).</li>,<li>Bug Fix load statistics graph links to include correct graph duration (regression in 2.277.1).</li>,<li>Bug Honor the current folder when creating new views with the "New View" link.</li>,<li>RFE Upgrade from xstream 1.4.15 to 1.4.16.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.277.4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.277.3]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Security Important security fix.</li>,<li>RFE Winstone 5.16: Update Jetty from 9.4.38.v20210224 to 9.4.39.v20210325 for bug fixes and enhancements.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.277.3</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.277.2]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Security Security fixes.</li>,<li>Major bug Fix help buttons in the draggable section (regression in 2.277.1).</li>,<li>RFE Security hardening against some CSRF attacks.</li>,<li>Bug Fix <code>NoClassDefFoundError</code> exception while executing <code>ProcessTree.get()</code>.</li>,<li>Bug Prevent Jenkins queue deadlock when cancelling tasks under certain conditions.</li>,<li>Bug Reduce logging of renamed API endpoint.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.277.2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.277.1]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Security Important security fix.
This vulnerability does not exist in any Jenkins LTS release.
It was discovered in a weekly release and fixed in a weekly release without being part of an LTS release.</li>,<li>Major bug Show available plugin updates by reloading update center data on upgrade/downgrade.</li>,<li>Major bug Fix Internet Explorer 11 rendering of the <em>Available</em> plugins tab (regression in 2.270).</li>,<li>Major bug Include 'plugin-id' and 'plugin-version' data attributes in the <em>Available</em> plugins tab (regression in 2.270).</li>,<li>Major bug Fix plugin search over multiple update sites (regression in 2.270).</li>,<li>Bug Restore, as deprecated, the old constructor based on acegisecurity <code>Authentication</code> parameter in order to keep backward compatibility.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.277.1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.263.4]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>RFE Improve performance in fingerprint file creation.</li>,<li>Bug Use the correct freestyle font-size for descriptions.</li>,<li>Bug Don't tell user's to signup when signup is not available.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.263.4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.263.3]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Security Security fix.</li>,<li>Major bug Provide a default implementation of the "all files in zip" download link.
This is especially important for external storage plugin (regression in 2.263.2).</li>,<li>Major bug Fix the file handle leak inside DirectoryBrowserSupport (regression in 2.263.2).</li>,<li>Major bug Include root folder in downloaded zip files (regression in 2.263.2).
Resolve an additional related zip archive root folder issue.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.263.3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.263.2]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Security Important security fixes.</li>,<li>Major bug Help text now expands in behaviours for GitHub organization folders (regression in 2.244).</li>,<li>RFE Security hardening related to XML processing using <code>Digester2</code>.</li>,<li>RFE Security hardening related to form validation responses.</li>,<li>RFE Security hardening restricting label names.</li>,<li>Bug Populate select fields with default values (regression in 2.244).</li>,<li>Bug Wrong unicode codes in Spanish translation and small improvements.</li>,<li>RFE Internal: Updated Node version to latest LTS (14.15.1).</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.263.2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.263.1]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Major bug Fix hidden page elements from radio blocks showing up when they should not.</li>,<li>Bug Fix file handle leak when viewing corrupted build logs.
Upgrade Stapler from 1.260 to 1.261.</li>,<li>Bug Prevent the Build History Widget from crashing when users have Discover permissions without Read for folders.</li>,<li>RFE Winstone 5.12: Update Jetty from 9.4.30.v20200611 to 9.4.33.v20201020.
Introduce LowResourceMonitor from Jetty by upgrading to Winstone 5.12.</li>,<li>RFE Improve performance of authorisation strategies when the authentication realm is case insensitive.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.263.1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.249.3]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Major bug Fix extensions footer location (regression in 2.235.1).</li>,<li>Major bug Show display names in change list again (regression in 2.249.1).</li>,<li>Bug Prevent radio buttons from moving when they are clicked.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.249.3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.249.2]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Major bug Fix migration of status filter when coming from an older version of Jenkins (regression in 2.249.1).</li>,<li>Bug Make alert colors consistent with 'Manage Jenkins' alert colors.</li>,<li>Bug Avoid warning on logs about Anonymous Class in <code>hudson.FilePath</code>.</li>,<li>Bug Fix NullPointerException pollution on logs if PluginDeprecationMonitor is enabled and some conditions are met.</li>,<li>Bug Developer: Make unavailable plugin background themeable.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.249.2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.249.1]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Security Important security fixes from Jenkins 2.252 and 2.235.4.</li>,<li>Major bug Stop pre-formatting agent logs to prevent deadlocks (regression in 2.231).</li>,<li>Major bug Fix button that copies API token to clipboard (regression in 2.238).</li>,<li>Major bug Restore wrapping tabs into multiple lines instead of overflowing (regression in 2.248).</li>,<li>Bug Normalize widget colors to be consistent with the new color palette.</li>,<li>Bug Empty installed plugins table text is readable again (regression in 2.249).</li>,<li>Bug Show build time data in the Build Time Trend Page (regression in 2.245).</li>,<li>Bug Replace text references to slave with agent in Japanese documentation and messages.</li>,<li>Bug Fix backspace key sometimes did not delete text from the Script Console on a Mac (regression in 2.248).</li>,<li>Bug Fix regular expression validator UI location (regression in 2.244).</li>,<li>RFE Prevent concurrent build deletion.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.249.1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.235.5]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Security Important security fixes.</li>,<li>Major RFE Major update of the Alpine-based Jenkins Docker image.
Jenkins Docker image for Alpine now uses Alpine 3.12 and AdoptOpenJDK 8u262.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.235.5</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.235.4]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Security Important security fixes.</li>,<li>Major RFE Use <strong>new 64 bit Windows installer</strong> with service account checks and port validation.
Supports 64 bit Java 8 and 64 bit Java 11.</li>,<li>Bug Allow graceful shutdown when SCM triggers are configured.</li>,<li>Bug Fix <code>IllegalArgumentException: Method not found</code> error caused by misbehaviour in <code>Util.isOverridden()</code> (regression in 2.241).</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.235.4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.235.3]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Major RFE Update Debian and Red Hat repository signing keys for the Jenkins long term support repositories.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.235.3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.235.2]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Security Important security fixes.</li>,<li>Bug Fix <code>--httpKeepAliveTimeout</code> option which had no effect (regression in 2.235.1).</li>,<li>Bug Fix buttons that linger too long after closing modal (regression in 2.233 and 2.235.1).</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.235.2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.235.1]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Major bug Make plugin manager work on Internet Explorer 11 again (regression in 2.231).</li>,<li>Major bug Prevent telemetry warnings about missing <code>javax.annotation</code> classes when running with Java 11 (regression in 2.231).</li>,<li>Major bug Fix a deadlock involving custom loggers during agent startup (regression in 2.231).</li>,<li>Bug Prevent Old Data Monitor from failing plugin loading in the case of class field unmarshalling issues.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.235.1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.222.4]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Major bug Prevent a form validation "404 Not Found" error when the resource root URL configuration points at a previously configured resource root URL (regression in 2.222.1).</li>,<li>Bug Upgrade to Remoting 4.2.1 to fix an issue with large payloads over WebSockets.
Requires a matching <code>agent.jar</code> with remoting 4.2.1 or later.</li>,<li>Bug Update Groovy Init hooks to run after all job configurations are adapted.</li>,<li>Bug Fix spacing between error messages in Setup Wizard (regression in 2.222.1).</li>,<li>Bug Fix input field hints for tools like the git plugin that search the PATH for their executable (regression in 2.222.1).</li>,<li>Bug Remove grey bar below the <code>textarea</code> form elements for read only users.</li>,<li>Bug Distinguish between defined (<strong>*****</strong>) and undefined (<strong>N/A</strong>) password on read-only configuration forms for users with Overall/SystemRead or Item/ExtendedRead permissions.</li>,<li>RFE Users with extended read permission now get a more read-only looking UI.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.222.4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.222.3]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Major bug Use the saved global build discarder configuration on restart.</li>,<li>Major bug Fix proxy form validation when a password is set (regression in 2.222.1).</li>,<li>Bug Prevent NullPointerException when hitting <em>Check Now</em> against a custom update center without tool installer metadata.</li>,<li>Bug Prevent one occurrence of "Jenkins.instance is missing" during Jenkins restart.</li>,<li>RFE Developer: Make <code>h.checkAnyPermission</code> and <code>&lt;l:layout permissions="..."&gt;</code> work on objects that aren't <code>AccessControlled</code>.</li>,<li>RFE Developer: Prevent spurious deprecation messages by removing the deprecated findbugs-annotation.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.222.3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.222.2]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Bug Jenkins 2.222.2 was not placed in the artifact repository or on the download site.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.222.2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.222.1]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Security Important security fixes.</li>,<li>Major bug Fix drag & drop for previously saved steps in the job configuration form (regression in 2.217).</li>,<li>Major bug Winstone 5.9: Fix propagation of the maximum form content size and form content keys number (regression in Jetty 9.4.20 and Jenkins 2.205).</li>,<li>Major bug Winstone 5.9: Fix improper reverse proxy redirects to host due to X-Forwarded-Host and X-Forwarded-Port ordering issue (regression in Jetty 9.4.20 and Jenkins 2.205).</li>,<li>RFE Security hardening related to request routing and CSRF protection.</li>,<li>RFE Developer: Listen on loopback interface by default in debug mode.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.222.1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.204.6]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Security Important security fixes.</li>,<li>RFE Security hardening related to request routing and CSRF protection.</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.204.6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.204.5]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Major bug Fix propagation of the maximum form content size and form content keys number (regression in Jetty 9.4.20 and Jenkins 2.204.3).</li>,<li>Major bug Fix improper reverse proxy redirects to 127.0.0.1 due to X-Forwarded-Host and X-Forwarded-Port ordering issue  (regression in Jetty 9.4.20 and Jenkins 2.204.3).</li>,<li>Bug Revert Winstone from 5.8 to 5.3 to resolve embedded Jetty web container regressions in later Winstone versions.
High default maximum form size limit and reverse proxy redirection are restored (regressions in 2.204.3).</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.204.5</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.204.4]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>Major bug Fix a <em>KeyStores with multiple certificates are not supported</em> error from Jetty when passing certain kinds of certificates, such as domain wildcards (regression in 2.204.3).</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.204.4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jenkins 2.204.3]]></title><description><![CDATA[<ul>
                    <li>RFE Internal: Winstone 5.7: Change the Jetty thread pool name to "Jetty (winstone)"</li>,<li>Bug If the Jenkins root URL has been configured by scripts prior to running the setup wizard, skip the location configuration panel even if selecting the option to skip creation of an admin user.</li>,<li>Bug Prevent inaccurate warnings about missing classes on Java 11 triggered by JavaMelody when Monitoring Plugin is installed.</li>,<li>Bug Include details in the system log when a build rotation fails.</li>,<li>Bug Fix java version check for AdoptOpenJDK 11.</li>,<li>Bug Prevent Jenkins page rendering from being blocked when the update center data parsing is in progress.</li>,<li>Bug Winstone 5.7: Fix support of system logging customization (regression in 2.177).</li>,<li>Bug Fix null pointer exception in Agent API when the agent is offline (e.g. retrieving agent version or OS description).</li>
                  </ul>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://halkeye.github.io/gatsby-jenkins-io/changelog-stable/#2.204.3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>